{
    "id": "479011ea70464af0a4061adaac99ee2a",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "....................... you have finished your work, you can go home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "When",
                "While",
                "Until"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ec2ce54e07b742478ddbd45a67d7fba6"
        },
        {
            "question": "Don’t talk ..................... they are singing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "during",
                "while"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "36527370dd43410dacb0c0d6a06ed60f"
        },
        {
            "question": "..................... he heard the news, he wrote to me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "As soon as",
                "When",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "87bbd272646b4a03ae2b667cc090e9c4"
        },
        {
            "question": "They were told to wait .....................… the signal was given.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "till",
                "until",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "25e0e54419134cf281096c097eb34389"
        },
        {
            "question": "Put it ………………….. you can find it again.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "where",
                "if"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "af5d89131d6e494c8b6f3c78f2b70d7d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will give you a map ..................... you can find the way.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "so that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f820de59a52d4073b3d7283a49235903"
        },
        {
            "question": "He thinks that he can buy justice ………………… he is rich.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "unless",
                "whether"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "94a47770be584fcabd7b799fe14bd365"
        },
        {
            "question": "You must go ..................... you hear from them or not.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "whether",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cdc0483d09694d639bfba07ae0f79feb"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will forgive you ....................... you do not repeat the offence.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on condition that",
                "in order that",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "91d21d314ced4e8a8e8985972de34c7a"
        },
        {
            "question": "They fought ....................... bravely that the enemy fled.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "too",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3350ac7a6a66468d81a5eb7c0f1f1a7a"
        }
    ]
}